# Nathan Childress



#### **About**

I am an Entrepreneur with a development background seeking an opportunity to apply my experience to software products. I faced problems with bad business models, tightening market space, undefined org structure and poor GTM. Learning to assess situations and correct mistakes, pivot products and refocus strategy I've successfully run the company at a profit for ten years. Now I would like to bring my experience and drive to a new company and team.

### Contact

T: 813-493-6283

r.nathanchildress@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /in/r-nathanchildress/

Bonney Lake, WA

## **Education**

UNIERSITY OF SOUTH FLORIDA All General Ed + Pre-requisite coursework in the College of Business Admin. (Marketing, Micro/Macro Economics, Managerial Accounting, Finance, Financial Accounting, Business Statistics.

# Experience

Founder - CEO nSource Services, Tampa, FL

10 years 2009-2020

- Created a marketing platform focused on the automotive retail industry. We created a single place the industry could gain insight on their target audience month over month by tracking all their marketing efforts across all channels.
- Grew company to 50 direct reports handling 2,800 direct and wholesale clients.
- Built sales team to launch B2B product. to sales of \$4MM in 12 months.
- Presented demos with executives in the automotive and advertising sectors.
- Planned comprehensive 1-6 month timelines + budgets for development with key milestones + requirements for launching features with development team.
- Based on feedback from clients, launched API and tools for clients to load their own data through the platform.
- Sought + Analyzed feedback from early adopters in order to improve upon UX.
- Created whitelabel price tier to wholesale clients based on analyzing customer needs and company financials to create a stable revenue stream with lower client churn.
- Developed lead ranking product. Product optimized queue to move the most customers through sales funnel. [Python, Twilio, .NET, SQL, IVR, CallRouting]
- Designed marketing materials and copy for customers and optimized for results with A/B testing.

.....

#### IT Manager\Developer

Innovative Technologies Group, Tampa, FL

4 Years 2005-2009

- Oversaw data center, managed team of onsite support techs, network
- Designed and developed the mobile client for logistics SaaS product Grower
- Lead Systems Design for launch of Grower Global Logistics software platform, now operating as a separate company Interstate Transport
- Product owner and Developer of Voice Research tool for Columbia University HIV research department for drug and patient habit use [VXML .NET]

•••••••••••••••••••••••

#### Quality Assurance

Fischer Identity, Naples,

2 Years

2000-2001

- Worked synchronizing systems with LDAP
- Created QA lab with development team to create testing protocols and lab to recreate customer environments (TCL, C, Windows, Unix)
- Maintained and wrote porting code changes between compiled environments.

Development	Management	Marketing
C#, Python, .Net, IIS, SQL, GIT, JQUERY, An- gular.JS HTML\CSS, GIT, Azure DB LDAP	Agile, SCRUM, #slack, Trello, SalseForceCRM, MSFT BI	MSFT BI, SQL SSMS, Adobe suite, Google Analytics, Journey Analytics